{
    "subject": "resource/Courteney_Cox",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1964-06-15",
    "human_readable": "Courteney Cox was born on June 15, 1964.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9246217012405396,
            "question": "When was Courteney Cox born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9068063497543335,
            "question": "In what year was Courteney Cox born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8229976892471313,
            "question": "What is Courteney Cox's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7978371381759644,
            "question": "What month was Courteney Cox born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7758471369743347,
            "question": "Was Courteney Cox born before or after 1965?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7297714948654175,
            "question": "What day of the week was Courteney Cox born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5827203392982483,
            "question": "How old would Courteney Cox be today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5460261702537537,
            "question": "Is Courteney Cox's birthday in the spring or summer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5359289646148682,
            "question": "Is Courteney Cox a summer baby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4416893720626831,
            "question": "If today is July 1st, is Courteney Cox's birthday past or future?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Courteney Cox was born on June 15, 1964.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7360_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Courteney Cox a summer baby?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7360_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Courteney Cox's birthday in the spring or summer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7360_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old would Courteney Cox be today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7360_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7360_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7360_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7360_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7360_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7360_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7360_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7360_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7360_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7360_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7360_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe triple is correct according to the documents. The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7360/re-ranker-msmarco/67.txt explicitly states that Courteney Bass COX was born on June 15, 1964 in Birmingham, Alabama, United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents consistently mention that Courteney Cox was born on June 15, 1964. This information is supported across multiple files, including \"72.txt\", \"15.txt\", \"83.txt\", and \"71.txt\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}